expertclick.com 2009-02-25

# Directory Of Experts - News Media Resource: Press Release Distribution and Journalist News Sources

|  | 

This site is operated by Broadcast Interview Source (Broadcast Interview Source is referred to herein as "we" or "us"). We respect the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices. 

Questions regarding privacy issues should be directed to us at ExpertClick@gmail.com. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with our site or to access those features that require registration. 

The information gathered by us falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to our website who either register to receive News Release Wire emails or to submit news release postings for display on the site, and (2) tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through our site. Third party service providers on, or linked to from, our website, such as vendors of products and services offered through our site, may be gathering the same kinds of information. 

To make use of certain features on our website (such as posting news releases or receiving selected News Release Wire emails) visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration process. This information may include your name, email address, zip code and credit card information. The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to make the site more useful to you, and to process e-commerce transactions. 

The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you don't supply the information we need to process your registration, we may be unable to provide you with the services you request. 

Of course, even if you want to remain completely anonymous, you're still free to take advantage of the wealth of content available on our site without registration. 

To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a sort of user ID, if you will, that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won't know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie can't read unrelated data off your hard drive. 

We use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs and to deliver a better, more personalized service. In addition, we may use cookies to track the pages on our site visited by our users. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our site. 

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site. 

And, of course, our site includes links to plenty of other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another website, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of that site. And when you provide information in the course of obtaining products or services through our site, use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those products or services, even if it appears that you're on our branded pages throughout the transaction. The provider's privacy policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our provider partners via a link either from the site's homepage or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information. 

Please note that we cannot guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a post news release that you post is available to anyone with Internet access. 

We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with applicable laws, to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our sites, the public, or Broadcast Interview Source. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event that Broadcast Interview Source, the bulk of our assets, or one or more of our sites is acquired by another company, information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets. 

A final note: The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes before they take effect. 

Of course, our use of information gathered while the current policy is in effect will always be consistent with the current policy, even if we change that policy later.   
  
---|---
